Seugnil Choi

697 bronx river rd, apt 312, Yonkers, NY 10704 | 607-206-6529 | schoi0115@gmail.com https://github.com/schoi0115 | https://medium.com/@schoi0115 | https://www.linkedin.com/in/choi-seungil/

PERSONAL DESCRIPTION

Experienced in Ruby on Rails and JavaScript based programming and a background in Arts and design. Possess strong skills in sales and financial management that help to see the customer's perspective. Having many years of website, sales, and finance management skills and love coding.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Ruby, Rails, SQL, Javscript, React

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

MBTA - https://github.com/schoi0115/MBTA

Tracking MBTA, Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority, and find your personal train schedule

• Example: Utilized JSON Web Tokens and localStorage to store encrypted user information client-side.

Photo-editor - https://github.com/schoi0115/Photo-editor

Be able to edit your local/url linked photo

Using useState to store images and editing with custom CSS code.

Project N - https://aithub.com/schoi0115/project-n| Demo

Nursing schedule checker for patients application

- Using bycript and localStorage to store user information.
- Using serialize creating validations
- Be able to schedule the nursing shift
- Checking and tracking hospitalized patients

App Name - https://github.com/schoi0115/medipill Demo

Personal medicine schedule log application

- Using bycript and localStorage to store user information.
- Using serializer creating validations

HomeGoods and HomeSense)

- Be able to add your medicine frequency system
- Be able to find local hospitals and pharmacies including your location

EXPERIENCE

BEST FINE ARTS, INC. Englewood, NJ

General Manager

01/2016 - 05/2018

• Developed and maintained business relationships with domestic and international companies (i.e, TJX: T.J. Maxx,

• Analyzed monthly and annual sales; performed monthly and yearly closing reports using Quickbooks

HRCAP, INC. Cliffside Park, NJ

Recruiter

01/2019 - 08/2019

- Interviewed potential candidates and reviewed plans for career growth; provided quick feedback for customer service
- Managed requisitions and offer process; maintained high-volume clientele and consulted with hiring managers

LIFETIME ARTS.

Office Manager

08/2019 - 02/2021

• Creates signed LOA, MOI, and MOU for Teaching Artists, 1099 employees contract

- Assist other teams' administrative tasks upon the request
- Quickbooks Tasks

EDUCATION

Flatiron School

Full Stack Web Development, Ruby on Rails and JavaScript program

New York, NY 10010
06/2021 - 10/2021